animal-space.net 2011-12-06

# Animal Space: Privacy Policy

This is the web site of Animal-space.net. This Policy is effective on March 10, 2010. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

**Our Commitment To Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Animal-space.net does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**Third Party Cookies**  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Animal-space.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. Animal-space.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Animal-space.net privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Animal-space.net. .:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to myfunnyworld.net and other sites on the Internet. .:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. Animal-space.net is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Contacting The Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can [contact us](http://www.animal-space.net/p/contact-us.html).
